[{"answer": " Hi, Danni.  What can I help you with today", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Well, Im about to graduate, and Im applying for jobs.  Ive worked a lot on m", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, Danni.  What can I help you with today", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " OK, sure.  What kind of help did you need with them", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Well, Im about to graduate, and Im applying for jobs.  Ive worked a lot on m", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Ive never really written one before, so I would like some help with what t", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " OK, sure.  What kind of help did you need with them", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " A cover letter is a very important part of your job application.  It covers the mai", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Ive never really written one before, so I would like some help with what t", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " OK.  How long should it be", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " A cover letter is a very important part of your job application.  It covers the mai", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " It shouldnt be longer than one page.  Employers dont have the time to rea", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " OK.  How long should it be", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " OK.  What should I include in my cover letter", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " It shouldnt be longer than one page.  Employers dont have the time to rea", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Your introductory paragraph should express your interest in the position, shoul", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " OK.  What should I include in my cover letter", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Do I discuss my qualifications in detail in the beginning", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Your introductory paragraph should express your interest in the position, shoul", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No, youll do that later in the letter.  In the introduction paragraph, you might wan", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Do I discuss my qualifications in detail in the beginning", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Oh, I understand", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": " No, youll do that later in the letter.  In the introduction paragraph, you might wan", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Your body paragraphs should emphasize your strongest qualifications an", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Oh, I understand", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " How much detail should I include", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Your body paragraphs should emphasize your strongest qualifications an", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Well, you want to be fairly brief, but you should elaborate on the information liste", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 54, "question": " How much detail should I include", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " So, just kind of re-word my resume in a letter format", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Well, you want to be fairly brief, but you should elaborate on the information liste", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " The cover letter is an opportunity to really show the employer specific, credibl", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " So, just kind of re-word my resume in a letter format", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Maybe instead of saying, I was a customer service representative at Pizz", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " The cover letter is an opportunity to really show the employer specific, credibl", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Bingo!  Thats exactly the kind of description that you want to include", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Maybe instead of saying, I was a customer service representative at Pizz", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " All right.  I think I understand that clearly then", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Bingo!  Thats exactly the kind of description that you want to include", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Another thing to remember is to coordinate the design of your letter with th", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " All right.  I think I understand that clearly then", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": "Is that really important", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Another thing to remember is to coordinate the design of your letter with th", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " If you do that, it looks very professional and can create a good impression", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is that really important", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": "  OK.  Ill do it", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " If you do that, it looks very professional and can create a good impression", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Finally, the most important thing to do is to carefully proofread your letter for an", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 81, "question": "  OK.  Ill do it", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I have a friend who said she would read over my letters for me to double-chec", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Finally, the most important thing to do is to carefully proofread your letter for an", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Thats a great idea.  If your letter has any errors in it, an employer is going to ge", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " I have a friend who said she would read over my letters for me to double-chec", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " No, I think you covered everything.  I have a good idea of what to include in on", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Thats a great idea.  If your letter has any errors in it, an employer is going to ge", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Good.  Good luck writing them and good luck with your job search", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 97, "question": " No, I think you covered everything.  I have a good idea of what to include in on", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Good.  Good luck writing them and good luck with your job search", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Youre welcome", "docId": "01-05", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 98}]
